https://tinsoldieruk.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Specials
PAINTED SHIPS & MORE...
15mm Carthaginian
15mm Celtic (400-150BC)
15mm Saxon
15mm Spanish (Punic)
15mm Sub-Roman (Brits)
25mm Etruscans
25mm Goths. Visigoths. Vandals.
Privacy Notice
This website uses the latest in Secure Server Technology to ensure that all personal and
transactional information is protected to the highest security standards.
Data Protection- in Summary
All personal details that you provide to us are held private between you and our online store,
we never make your personal details available to other companies for marketing purposes.
We may hold your personal details in order to process your order and/or maintain your account.
Cookies
As part of our high security standards, all session information is stored in our system database
whenever possible, with the use of Cookies being kept to an absolute minimum.
Keeping In Touch With You
We will email you with your account and login information when you register with our online shop.
Where you have opted-in to receive our Newsletter we will periodically send you information about
products, and promotional offers that you might be interested in.
If you prefer not to receive such information or be a part of such research at any time,
please email to "unsubscribe" quoting your full name, address and postcode
Update to reflect new GDPR Regulations as from 25th May 2018
What is Personal Data?
Under the EU General Data Protection Regulation personal data is defined as: Any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (data subject).
Why do Tin Soldier UK need to collect and store my data?
For you to be a customer of Tin Soldier UK we need to hold certain information such as contact name/names, address, phone numbers, email addresses. We need this so we an contact you regarding offers, orders, shipping and any other day to day account management.
Will Tin Soldier UK share my personal data with anyone else?
No
How long is my personal information retained for?
Tin Soldier UK will process (collect, store and use) the information you provide in a manner compatible with the EU General Data Protection Regulation. We will endeavour to keep your information accurate and up to date, and not keep it for longer than is necessary.
Under what circumstances will Tin Soldier UK contact me?
Our aim is not to be intrusive, and we undertake not to ask irrelevant or unnecessary questions. Moreover, the information you provide will be subject to measures and procedures to minimise the risk of unauthorised access and disclosure. We will continue to contact you from time to time to if you have opted in to newsletters.
What are my rights as a data subject?
At any point while we are in the possession of or processing your personal data, you, the data subject, have the following rights:
Right of access - you have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you.
Right of rectification - you have the right to correct data that we hold about you that is inaccurate or incomplete. If at any point you become aware that any of the personal data we hold in respect of you is inaccurate, then please call or email us via the contact details below whereby, once verified, we will arrange for the information to be updated.
Right to be forgotten - in certain circumstances you can ask for the data we hold about you to be erased from our records.
Right to restriction of processing - where certain conditions apply to have a right to restrict the processing.
Right to object - you have the right to object to certain types of processing such as direct marketing.
Right to object to automate processing, including profiling -you also have the right to be subject to the legal effects of automated processing or profiling.
Right to judicial review - in the event that refuses your request under rights of access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. You have the right to complain as mentioned below. All the above requests will be forwarded on should there be a third party involved (as stated above) in the processing of your personal data.
Can I find out what personal data the company holds about me?
At your request Tin Soldier UK can confirm what information we hold about you and how it is processed. If Tin Soldier UK does hold personal data about you, you can request the following information:
Identity and the contact details of the person that has determined how and why to process data.
Contact details of the data protection representative, where applicable.
The purpose of the processing as well as the legal basis for processing.
The categories of personal data collected, stored and processed.
Categories of recipients that the data is/will be disclosed to.
How long the data will be stored.
Details of your rights to correct, erase, restrict or object to such processing.
Information about your right to withdraw consent at any time.
How to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority.
Whether the provision of personal data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract, as well as whether you are obliged to provide the personal data and the possible consequences of failing to provide such data.
The source of personal data if it was not collected directly from you.
Any details and information of automated decision making, such as profiling, and any meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and expected consequences of such processing.
How can I make a complaint?
In the event that you wish to make a complaint about how your personal data is being processed by Tin Soldier UK, or how your complaint has been handled, you have the right to lodge a complaint directly with the Tin Soldier UK.
Back
Shop
Home
Featured
Specials
New Arrivals
View All
Customer Service
TIN SOLDIER (U.K.)
